你全身泡泡好可爱
You look cute in bubbles.
你喝太多眼花了
You're just all liquored up.
是我，我进去了
Hey,it's me. I'm coming in.
我今天上班累死了
I've had a very long,hard day.
你提早回家
-You're home early.
因为我的约会对象吐了一地
-Yeah,my date threw up.
我要去买炸鸡，你要不要？
Want some chicken?
不了，谢谢，再见
No,thanks. No chicken. Bye-bye.
你确定？有额外的脆脆的大米哦？
You sure? Some extra-crispy,dirty rice?
我最后一次说我不要了 出去，乔伊
For the last time,no! Get out,Joey!
知道了
All right.
你没事吧？抱歉，他死都不走 缠着我问要不要炸鸡
Are you okay? I'm so sorry!He wouldn't leave.He kept asking me if I wanted chicken.
炸鸡？
Chicken?
我想吃炸鸡
I could eat some chicken.
乔伊
Hey Joey
我要三块鸡、沙拉 豆子、可乐
Could I get a three-piece,some coleslaw,some beans and a Coke?
健怡可乐
Diet Coke.
本集播出：“热吻连连”
The One With All the Kissing
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库桌
麦特勒布蘭
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
早安
-Morning,
早安，菲比
Phoebe.
我非告诉你们不可
-I have to tell you this story.
刚才载我来的司机…
I was coming over and this cabdriver
那人是不是叫做安格斯？
Was his name Angus?
什么？
What?
我们在伦敦碰到的计程车司机
He was a cabdriver we had in London.
好吧，总之…
All right. Anyway
他载我们去的酒馆叫什么？
What was that pub he took us to?
麦子酒馆
The Wheat Sheaf!
对，那里有一种啤酒…
And they had that beer....
柏丁顿
Boddington's!
就是柏丁顿
菲比有话要说
Phoebe was going to tell a story.
他的帽子很好笑… 我不想说了
So he had a really funny hat.I don't want to talk about it.
罗斯，柏丁顿
-Hey. -Hey,Ross!Boddington's!
是啊
Oh,man!
若是能再喝一杯 要我走回伦敦都行
I'd walk back to London for another frosty one of those bad boys.
世贸附近的英国酒馆好像有
They have them at the British pub by the Trade Center.
回头见
Later!
瑞秋不是应该回来了吗？
Shouldn't Rachel be back?
可是班机在雅典误点
Her plane got delayed.
不过现在也该到了
But she should be here by now.
你跟她通过电话 她很生气吗？
So you talked to her? Did she sound mad?
不会，那是因为她喜欢我
No. But she likes me.
你丢下她让她独自飞到希腊去
You abandoned her on a plane to Greece.
我才没有丢下瑞秋
I did not "abandon" Rachel. Okay?
艾蜜莉出现在机场 我当然得去追她
Emily showed up at the airport.I had to go after her.
我别无选择 毕竟她是我妻子，瑞秋是我妻子
I did what I had to do.She's my wife. Rachel is my wife.
是…艾蜜莉
Emily!
艾蜜莉是我老婆 我是怎么了？
Emily is my wife.Man,what is that?
你还没有艾蜜莉的消息？
You haven't heard from Emily?
我在机场追丢之后就没有了
Not since I lost her at the airport.
她竟然跑得比你快
I can't believe she can outrun you.
她是很快，好吗？
Hey! She's fast,okay?
你自以为能快过我？ 我们现在就去外头较量
You think you can beat me? Let's go! Outside!
抱歉，我太…
-I'm sorry. I'm just a little
慢了？
-Slow?
你要跟我比比吗？
Oh,you want some?!
走啊，去穿球鞋，我们去赛跑
Okay,get the shoes on! Let's go,man!
别激动，你跑得最快
It's cool,okay?You're the fastest!
嗨
-Hi!
瑞秋 嗨
-Oh,my God,Rachel!
瑞秋，我很抱歉
Rach,I am so sorry.
非常对不起你
I am so,so sorry.
罗斯，你没做错
Come on. You just did what you had to do.
嗨，菲比
Hi，Phoebe
就这样？你不生气？
That's it? You're not mad?
你应该很火大
It must've been terrible.
火大？我可是在希腊
Terrible? Hell,I was in Greece!
那间饭店非常棒 海滩很美，人又和善
There was a nice hotel,nice beach,met the nice people.
对我瑞秋来说可不差
It's not too shabby for Rachel.
就这样？不生气？
So,what,that's it?
对，我没生你的气
We're cool. Totally cool.
谢谢，你真好
Thanks,Rach. You're the best.
你才好呢
Oh,no. You're the best.
我要去花店一趟
Oh,I got to go to the flower store.
听我说，大家都不肯说 艾蜜莉在哪里
No one will tell me where Emily is...
我决定买72朵长茎红玫瑰 送去艾蜜莉爸妈家
...so I'm sending 72 long-stemmed,red roses to her parents' house.
每朵代表我认识她 并且深爱她的每一天
One for each day I've known and loved her.
她一定会感动地软化
That should get her talking.
罗斯，写卡片时别忘了 对方是“艾蜜莉”
When you make out the card,be sure to make it out to "Emily."
瑞秋，太好了 幸好你在希腊玩得开心
It's good that you had such a good time in Greece.
什么？
What?
我在希腊才不开心
I didn't have a good time in Greece!
罗斯丢下我一人
Ross abandoned me!
我买不到机票回来 只好住在他们的蜜月套房
I couldn't get a plane out. I had to stay in their suite!
每个人都要来问我
People came up to me going,
“盖勒太太，你哭什么？”
"Mrs. Geller! Why are you cry?"
简直丢死人了，我真是个白痴
I mean,it was so humiliating!I felt like such an idiot!
这都是我的错
It's all my fault.
你们知道为什么吗？ 因为我的决定都不对
You know why?Because I make very bad decisions.
不要这么说
Oh,that's not true.
就是这样，我没胡说 我跑去蠢伦敦追罗斯
Yes,it is true. I went after Ross in stupid London!
伦敦的确是个蠢地方！太蠢了
London is stupid! Stupid!
打扮得像个啦啦队长 倒追约书亚
I put on a cheerleading outfit to seduce Joshua.
约了四次会就叫他娶我 把他吓死了
Then I lost him because I asked him to marry me after four dates.
然后我还去希腊渡别人的蜜月
And then I went to Greece on somebody else's honeymoon. Okay?
你们觉得这些决定正确吗？
Do those sound like very good decisions to you?
我喜欢你的小辫子
I like your little braid.
我不应该做任何决定
I just shouldn't be allowed to make decisions anymore.
菲比，你说得对 我根本不该去伦敦
Phoebe,you were right. I should've never gone to London.
从现在开始由你帮我做决定
From now on,you make all my decisions for me.
不行，我以前就这么做过
Oh,no. I did that for someone once.
我不喜欢主宰别人的生活
I'm not comfortable having that power over someone's life.
那我来
I'll do it.
很好，莫妮卡 以后由你主宰我的感情生活
Fine. Monica,you are now in charge of my love life.
我该去上班了
Okay. I got to go to work.
瑞秋，很高兴看到你回来
And Rachel,great to have you back.
菲比
Phoebe
真开心
Always a pleasure.
瑞秋，亲爱的，你看
Rachel? Sweetie,look.
这是你跟乔伊在招待会的照片
Here's a cute picture of you and Joey.
他已经结婚了
He's married.
罗斯结婚了 我到现在还不敢相信
Ross is married. I still can't believe it.
亲爱的，抓旁边就好
Honey,sweetie,by the edges.
看来我只好接受事实
I'll just have to accept it.
这都要怪我
I mean,it's my fault.
别抓中间，指纹会弄脏照片
Edges! Fingers! Smudgy!
天啊
Oh,my God!
算了
That's okay.
我知道你心情低落 不是故意找我麻烦
I know that you're very upset right now.I know that wasn't about me.
我看她就是跟她作对
I bet it was about her a little.
你要是肯放下罗斯一分钟 就会发现到处有帅哥
If you'd stop thinking about Ross...you'd notice there are great guys everywhere.
你看，例如甘瑟
Look. Gunther.
他既善良又可爱
He's nice. He's cute.
甘瑟的确…
Yeah. I guess Gunther is....
还有那边那个家伙
What about that guy over there?
记得吗？你以前 跟他打情骂俏过
That's the guy you flirted with at the counter.
我不知道…
-Oh,I don't know. I don't know.
你现在就去跟他说话
-You're going to talk to him.
我们说好由我发号施令 我命令你去跟他说话
I make your decisions,and I say you're going to talk to him.
好吧，你说了算
All right.You're the boss.
看来我只好照办
I got to do what you tell me.
他听到这句话肯定上钩
Say that to him,and you're golden.
菲比
Hey,Phoebe.
伦敦的照片洗出来了
We got our pictures back from London.
这张是所有人在伦敦塔拍的
Here's all of us at the Tower of London....
大家都在照片中
Here we all are.
有罗斯、乔伊、你…
There's Ross and Joey and you and
和我
And me.
你一定听烦我们说伦敦的事了
We've been talking about London too much.
是我不好，因为我去不了
Sorry,it's just because I couldn't be there.
我只能大着肚子 烦都快烦死了
All I get to do now is pregnant stuff. It bums me out.
很抱歉…
-I'm sorry. -Sorry.
你知道我伤心时都怎么做吗？
Know what I like to do?
有时候事情不太顺利
It sounds a little corny...but sometimes when I'm bummed out,
我就闭上眼睛 想想人生实在挺美好
I like to just close my eyes...and think about what a wonderful gift life is.
有用吧？
See?
怎么样？
-What happened?
总之我们东扯西扯
-A little of this,a little of that.
明天晚上要出去约会
I got myself a date tomorrow.
看吧？你就要忘记罗斯了
See? Didn't I tell you? You're getting over Ross already.
滚出去 “我们有权利拒绝服务”
Get out.
你怎么去那么久？
What took so long?
公事担搁了
I got caught up at work.
不过我明天就辞职
But I'm quitting tomorrow.
谢谢你邀我过来
So thanks for having me over.
瑞秋
Rachel
菲比
Phoebe
再见
See you,man.
他发什么神经？
What the hell was that?
可能在伦敦学到的欧洲风俗
Probably some European goodbye thing he picked up in London.
那才不是欧洲风俗
That's not European.
比较像法式热吻
It felt French.
换我跟各位老友说再见了
Well,I guess it's time for me to say goodbye too,mon frere.
过来给我点甜头吧
Come here and give me a little sugar.
我玩得好开心
I really had a good time.
我也是
Yeah,me too.
看来今天要结束了
I guess this is it.
除非你想进来 好
Unless you want to come inside? Yeah
等等，我无法自做主张
Wait a minute. You know what? I can't decide this.
等我一下 好
Okay. Just hold on a second.
莫妮卡在吗？我有事要问她
Where's Monica? I have to ask her something.
她去洗衣服
Doing her laundry.
那是什么？
What's that?
我今天收到的包裹
It came in the mail today.
72朵代表我深爱艾蜜莉 的红玫瑰给剪成碎片
It's 72 long-stemmed red roses.One for each day I've known and loved Emily cut up into mulch.
真是糟糕
Honey,that's awful.
还好啦，莫妮卡要用来做香料
It's not so bad.Monica's going to make potpourri.
我要去淋雨散散心
I think I'm going to go wander out in the rain for a while.
外面没下雨
It's not raining.
我的运气真不好
I can't catch a break!
罗斯，你哪也别去
You're not going anywhere.
就坐这里 我们喝茶聊天，好吗？
Sit right here.I'll make you some tea and we'll talk this out.All right?
大卫 怎么样？
Hey,Dave.
改天再请你进来 我的室友病得很重，再见
I need to take a rain check. My roommate is really sick.Okay. Bye!
亲爱的，听着，我知道你现在一定很伤心
Honey,listen.I know things seem so bad...and that they won't get any
瑞秋
Rachel
我可以跟你谈谈吗？
Could I talk to you?
我掉了几支袜子
I dropped some socks.
好
Ya
你哪根筋不对？
What is the matter with you?
你又想跳回去自找苦吃？
Do you want to fall into the trap?
你根本没掉袜子
You did not drop any socks!
我刚碰到大卫 他说你打发他走
I saw Dave,and he said you blew him off!
你给我听好，这里由我当家
You listen to me!I'm calling the shots!
我要你离开罗斯去追大卫
I say you leave Ross and go get Dave.
你到底想怎么样？
What are you doing?
其实我想…我打算…
Well,ultimately I was trying,you know,I wanted...
告诉他我还爱他
...to tell him that I'm still in love with him.
什么？你不准说
What? You cannot tell him that!
为什么？ 大家都喜欢听到这种话
Why? Why not?People love to hear that!
我爱你
Come on,I love you.
你不喜欢听吗？
-Wasn't that nice? -No.
这里由我做决定，我不准你说
I make the decisions and I say no!
你不能帮我做决定 因为我要开除你
You know what? No,you don't make my decisions,because...you're fired.
你不能开除我
You can't fire me.
你的事情由我来决定 我说：我没被开除
I make your decisions,and I say I'm not fired! Ha!
既然如此…
Well....
瑞秋，让我进去
Come on,let me in!
怎么了？
Having some trouble?
瑞秋把我锁在门外
Rachel locked the door.
你肯亲我，我就帮你撞开
I'll kick that door in if you give me some sugar.
罗斯，我有话要告诉你
Ross,there's something I wanna talk to you about.I just need to
瑞秋，开门！
Rachel,open this door!
门锁着吗？
-What,is it locked?
别管她，听我说
-She's fine. Listen....
我可以在外面鬼叫一整晚
Rachel,I can do this all night if I have to!
要不要我去开门？
-You want me to get that?
别理她，我们说我们的
No. Just let her do her thing...and we'll do our thing.
我要告诉你…
Because I really need to tell you
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋，我可以跟你谈谈吗？
Rachel? Can I talk to you outside for a sec?
不可以
No
我真的有话要跟你说
We really need to talk.
那就说啊 那我就说咯
Well,then talk.Okay,I will.
记得我们刚说你要做的事吗？
Remember that thing we just discussed that you wanted to do?
记得
Yes
什么事？
What thing?
瑞秋要去学摇摆舞
Rachel wants to take swing dance lessons.
我非常不赞成
Which I think is a really stupid idea.
因为这种舞很危险
It's dangerous.
她一定学不会 而且搞不好还会撞伤人
She won't get what she wants.And who knows who she might end up hurting?
莫妮卡说得对 摇摆舞有点危险
Monica's right. Swing dancing can be tricky.
我要打电话取消 五只送给艾蜜莉的泰迪熊
I have to use the phone.I gotta cancel those five giant teddy bears I sent to Emily.
上帝啊，想想这个惨状
My God! Think of the massacre.
我就是要说
I'm going to do it.
瑞秋，我知道你认为我疯了
I know you think I'm crazy.
但是在你告诉他之前 至少找到一个人支持你
But before you tell him,try to find one person...who thinks it's a good idea.
我打赌你找不到
I bet you can't.
可是… 拜托
But I…Please?
好吧
All right. Fine.
乔伊，我已经进来了
Joey! I'm in!
好，做得好
All right. Good deal.
瑞秋
-Hi. -Hey,Rach.
你找到谁支持你了吗？
-Did you find anyone who agrees with you?
还没，我决定问男性的意见
No.But you know what? I think I need a male point of view.
乔伊
Joey.
你是男人
-You're a man.
货真价实
-You got that right.
你觉得我该告诉罗斯 我还爱他吗？
Do you think it would be a good idea if I told Ross that I was still in love with him?
不
Nope.
菲比
-Phoebe! -Hey,Phoebe.
菲比 怎样？
-Phoebe? -Yeah.
你上次说你都不能去伦敦 觉得自己遭大家遗弃
You know how you were saying you didn't get to go to London...and you were feeling left out?
如何？
Ya
我们很愧疚
Well,we all felt really bad about that...
决定大家一起去旅行
...so we decided to take a little trip together!
太好了
Oh,that's so nice!
要去哪里？…
How great! Where's the trip?
我们可以一起去野餐
Well,we thought we would all go to a picnic...
就去中央公园
...in Central Park!
中央…公园
Central Park?
对，大家一起去个一整天
All of us. All day.
什么鸟地方？！
That sucks!
那根本不算旅行 我才刚从公园过来
That's not a trip! I just came from there.
大家去中央公园有什么好兴奋
What'll we high-five about at the stupid park?
“好耶，就在我家旁边”
It's right by my house. All right!
我决定回家反省这个烂主意
I'm going home to bask in the triumph of my Central Park idea.
等一下，热吻先生
Hold on a sec there,Mr. Kissy.
我一直想跟你讨论 你新学的欧洲民情
I wanted to talk to you about...this whole new European thing you've got going on.
你搞得我非常不自在 拜托你别再亲了
And I need to say it makes me very uncomfortable...and I just,you know,just stop it!
我只是想 介绍大家认识欧洲文化
Just bringing some culture to the group.
只要不要介绍到我嘴里就好了
That's fine. Just don't bring it in my mouth.
我都快吐了
It makes me want to puke.
各位，菲比来了
Hey,everybody! Phoebe is here!
菲比！嗨
-Phoebe! Woo! -Okay. Woo! Hi!
我们认为野餐的主意… 实在烂透了
Phoebe,we decided that the picnic idea was a little....It didn't have any.... Well,it blew.
所以今天下午决定 到大西洋城去渡周末
We thought that this afternoon we'd all go away for the whole weekend...to Atlantic City.
大西洋城，太好了 谁想到的？
Atlantic City! Oh,that's a great plan! Whose plan was that?
我
Mine!
等等，是我提议的
-Wait. It was my plan.
错 我说我们应该想个新的计划
-No...I said we needed a new plan.
然后我想到要去大西洋城
And I came up with Atlantic City.
这就是新的计划啊
Which is the new plan.
大家一小时后楼上见
Why don't we all meet upstairs in an hour.
我要去打包了 我要摇着大屁股好好打包
I'm going to go pack. I'm going to go pack my ass off.
我去叫杯咖啡 因为我已经摇屁股打包完了
Well,I think I'm gonna grab some coffee because my ass is already packed.
瑞秋，我们走吧
Let's go.
我等一下再上去找你
You know what? I'll meet you in a minute.
不行，瑞秋，没有人支持你 所以你不能说
Rachel,you didn't find anyone,so you can't tell him.
无所谓
You know what? That doesn't matter.
你知道对方不能回应你的爱意 会有多痛苦吗？
Do you know how painful it is to tell someone you love them...and not have them say it back?
知道，我不在乎
I don't care.
好吧，可是我看不下去
I can't watch.
你在看什么？
What you reading?
报纸 上面说了什么？
Paper.Yeah? What's it about?
世界各地的新闻
Events from around the globe.
是啊
Okey
罗斯，我有件事要告诉你
There's something I have to talk to you about.
虽然大家都叫我别说
Everyone's saying I shouldn't.
但是他们都错了 有时候别人就是看不清楚
But I think they're wrong. People can be wrong.
当然，有一次上班时 我说放射性碳测定法太老旧…
Sure，Once at work...I thought carbon dating is fossilized
罗斯，我说正经的
I'm really trying to tell you something here.
说吧
Go ahead.
我这就说了，现在就告诉你
I think I'm just going to say it.I'm just going to say it.
我还爱着你，罗斯
I'm still in love with you,Ross.
我不知道现在该怎么回答
I'm not sure what to do with that right now.
怎么了？你跟我开玩笑？ 这就太恶劣了
What? Was that a joke? Because it's mean.
我很正经，不能再正经了
I'm so dead serious!I'm totally serious!
那你笑什么？
Why are you laughing?
因为我刚听到自己的话
Because I just heard it!
我听到了，而且觉得很荒谬
I heard it. And it's ridiculous!
毕竟你已经结婚
I mean....You're married!
你结婚了，我说这话太可笑
You're married,and it's just ridiculous!
我说话的时候似乎灵魂出壳
When I said it,I sort of floated up out of my body.
我的灵魂听到肉身说话
And then I heard myself say it,and then the floating Rachel....
瑞秋的灵魂认为 自己实在很白痴
I was like,"You are such an idiot!"
我的确已经结婚。我知道
-Well,I am married. -I know.
虽然婚礼后就没跟老婆说过话
Though I haven't spoken to her since the wedding.
抱歉，这不好笑
I'm sorry. That's not funny.
其实还蛮好笑的
Actually,it kind of is.
我老婆不回我电话
My wife won't return my calls.
我不知道老婆在哪里
I don't know where my wife is.
“罗斯，你老婆呢？” 我也不知道
"Hey,Ross! Where's the missus?" "Don't know!"
天啊
Oh,God!
你可以忘记我刚说的话吗？
You know what? Could you forget I told you this?
我不忘记也不行 因为事实是…
Well,I kind of have to.Because the thing is
事实就是你已经娶了艾蜜莉
The thing is,you know,that you're married to Emily.
事实正是如此
That is what the thing is.
天啊
Oh,God.
罗斯，我们还是好朋友吧 我说自己还爱你真是蠢毙了
Things won't be weird between us,right? Was that stupid?Me telling you that?
不会，我很高兴你告诉我
I'm glad you did.
就算日子很顺利 听到有人说爱你还是很开心
If nothing else...it's always great when someone tells you they love you.
我早说过了
That's what I said!
谢谢你对我这么好
-Thank you for being so nice.
我才该谢谢你
-No. Thank you for....
谢谢你
Thank you.
幸好我没给你 我录的那卷录音带
Oh,God. I'm just glad I didn't give you the cassette I made of all of our songs.
你录了哪些歌曲？
-What songs? -Oh,you know:
“有没有你”
-"With or Without You." -Oh,yeah.
“大家都会受伤”
-"Everybody Hurts." -Oh,yeah.
“瑞安娜”
-"Rhiannon."
为什么选这首？
-Why "Rhiannon"?
你不记得了？
Come on,you remember!
就是在客厅啊
In the living room?
在莫妮卡洗好的衣服上啊
On Monica's laundry?
那不是我
Not me.
不是？
Really.
怎么样了？
So,what happened?
我很难说出口
Well,it was really hard...
但是幸好我说了
...but I'm glad I did it.
你做得对吗？
So was I right or wrong?
这种事情无关对错
-Oh,come on,honey,does it really matter?
是啊 没错
-No.-Right
但是我要记在记分簿上
Yes. I need it for my score book.
我是说日记
Diary.
大家走吧
-Okay,let's go!
前往大西洋城
-Yeah,Atlantic City!Come on!
去大西洋城咯
Atlantic City,baby!
我们去大赌一笔 乔伊，赌博万岁
Let's roll some bones. Hey,Joey!High-five for rolling bones.
菲比，你尿失禁？
Phoebe,you're leaking.
天啊，你羊水破了
Oh,my God! Your water broke!
别放在心上，我要坐副驾驶！
Well,don't worry. I call shotgun.
等一下
Wait
菲比，我们得送你去医院
Phoebe,we have to take you to the hospital now.
去大西洋城路上应该有医院
Okay. Well,there's probably one on the way to Atlantic City.
菲比，你快要生了
Phoebe,the babies are coming now.
击掌，你要生了！
Honey! High-five! The babies are coming!
等一下，记不记得 我羊水破的那天？
Remember when my water broke?
菲比竟然快生了
I can't believe Phoebe's going to have her babies!
我知道，真是太棒了
I know. It's beautiful and amazing.
你知道吗，我竟然每次离开 都得亲菲比跟瑞秋
I can't believe I had to kiss Phoebe and Rachel every time I left the room.
可惜她们没看到我们做爱
It's too bad they didn't see us having sex.
你到底了不了解女人？
Do you know anything about women?
不了解
No
算了 好
-It's all right. -Okay.